Everyone has a hero withing them.
Be Here Now is a documentary film directed by Lilibet Foster.
An inspiring feature documentary and love story, about the overnight sensation, actor and international sex symbol, Andy Whitfield, who put
the same determination and dedication that he brought to his lead role in "Spartacus" into fighting life-threatening cancer.
Himself, played by Andy Whitfield.
Himself, played by Jai Courtney.
Herself, played by Indigo Whitfield.
Himself, played by Jesse Whitfield.
Herself, played by Pat Whitfield.
Himself, played by Robert Whitfield.
Be Here Now may refer to:
Be Here Now (book), a 1971 book on spirituality by Ram Dass
Be Here Now, a 2015 documentary
film about actor Andy Whitfield having cancer
Be Here Now, a 2017 dance work choreographed by Trey McIntyre
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship, biography,
cancer, struggle for survival, terminal cancer.
The tone is uplifting.